A Guide to the Trust for Mutual Understanding records FA412
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1970, 1975, 1978, 1982, 1987-2012; 3; 45.95 Cubic Feet 121 letter document boxes
  - Arena Dances, Miscellaneous, Open Look, DF-0800, 2005, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 281)
  - Arena Stage, EC-0101, 2000-2003 (Box 26, Folder 282)
  - Arena Stage, DF-0616, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 283)
  - ART/OMI, Cimelice Castle Residency, DF-0117, 2001-2003 (Box 26, Folder 284)
  - Art in General, B-0042, B-0181, B-0274, 2000-2006 (Box 26, Folder 285)
  - Art in General, B-0306, B-0401, B-0500, 2003-2007 (Box 26, Folder 286-287)
  - Art in General, B-0306, B-0401, B-0500; Art in General, Eastern European Residency Exchanges (Box 26, Folder 286)
  - Art in General, B-0306, B-0401, B-0500; Art in General, Images from EERE Program, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 286)
  - Art in General, B-0306, B-0401, B-0500, Art in General, Rafal Bujnowski Images (Box 26, Folder 286)
  - Art In General, Miscellaneous, B-0306, B-0401, B-0500, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 288)
  - Art in General, Miscellaneous, B-0401, Art in General, Eastern European Residency Roundtable Discussion, 2005 May 31; 2011:012:009 (Box 26, Folder 288)
  - Art in General, B-0653, B-0704, 2002-2004, 2006-2009 (Box 26, Folder 289)
  - Art in General, Miscellaneous, B-0653, B-0704, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 290)
  - Art in General, B-0855, 2008-2010 (Box 27, Folder 291)
  - Art in General, Miscellaneous, B-0855, 2000-2003, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 292)
  - Art in General, Miscellaneous, Eastern European Residency Exchange (EERE), 2002-2007, 2002, 2004, 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 293)
  - Artists Space, DF-0646, 2005-2008 (Box 27, Folder 295)
  - Arts Council of Mongolia U.S., B-0543, 2003, 2005-2007 (Box 27, Folder 295)
  - Arts Council of Mongolia U.S., B-0543, Arts Council of Mongolia-U.S., Tumen Eleh Tour, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 295)
  - Arts International/FACE Croatia, B-0059, B-01117, B-0255, B-0374, 2000-2006 (Box 27, Folder 296)
  - Arts International/FACE Croatia, B-0059, B-01117, B-0255, B-0374, Kristin Leko on Milk 2 People PPS (Box 27, Folder 296)
  - Arts International, "American Season", B-0215, B-0301, 2002-2008 (Box 27, Folder 297-298)
  - Arts International, Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 299)
  - Arts International, "Here Tomorrow", DF-0212, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 300)
  - Arts International. "Here Tomorrow", DF-0212, Here Tomorrow, Exhibition Opening and Events, 2002 October 4 (Box 27, Folder 300)
  - Arts International, Pristina Theater Project, EC-0301, 2003-2004, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 301)
  - Arts International, EC-0326, 2002-2005 (Box 28, Folder 302)
  - Arts Midwest, B-0117, 2000-2004 (Box 28, Folder 303)
  - Arts Midwest, B-0117, Traveling Christmas Tree (Box 28, Folder 303)
  - ArtSpot Productions, B-0605, 2001-2004, 2006, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 304)
  - Asia Society, DF-0337, 2003-2004, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 305)
  - Association for the Protection of the Adirondacks, B-0261, 2002-2003, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 306)
  - Assumption College, DF-0711, 2006-2007 (Box 28, Folder 307)
  - Atlantic States Legal Foundation, B-02100, 2002-2007 (Box 28, Folder 308)
  - August Strindberg Society of Los Angeles, DF-0344, 2003-2005 (Box 28, Folder 309)
  - August Strindberg Society of Los Angeles, Miscellaneous, DF-0344, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 310)
  - Auschwitz Jewish Center Foundation, B-0277, 1999-2000, 2002-2003, 2006-2007 (Box 28, Folder 311)
  - Backlot Arts, DF-0731, 2007, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 312)
  - Backlot Arts, Miscellaneous, DF-0731, 1999, 2001, 2003-2004, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 313)
  - Baikal Watch, DF-0210, 2002, 2006-2007 (Box 29, Folder 314)
  - The George Balanchine Foundation, EC-0402, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 315)
  - The George Balanchine Foundation, Miscellaneous, EC-0402, 2002-2003, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 316)
  - Bang on a Can, DF-0126, 2001-2003 (Box 29, Folder 317)
  - Bang on a Can, B-0278, 2002-2004 (Box 29, Folder 318)
  - Bang on a Can, Tour with Iva Bittova, DF-0515, 2005, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 319)
  - Bang on a Can, DF-0539, 2004-2006, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 320)
  - Bang on a Can, DF-0617, 2005-2006 (Box 29, Folder 321)
  - Bank Information Center, B-0369, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 322)
  - Bank Information Center, B-0472, 2002, 2004-2006 (Box 29, Folder 324)
  - Bank Information Center, B-0571, 2005-2007 (Box 29, Folder 324)
  - Bank Information Center, B-0669, 2006-2008 (Box 29, Folder 325)
  - Bank Information Center, B-0773, 2007-2009 (Box 29, Folder 326)
  - Bard College, Alternativa Festival, B-0235, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 327)
  - Bard College, Douglas Davis, DF-0221, 2001-2003, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 328)
  - Bard College, Fischer Center for the Performing Arts, DF-0236, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 329)
  - Bard College, B-0307, 1994, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 330)
  - Bard College, Sarajevo Self Portrait, DF-0325, 2001, 2003-2006 (Box 30, Folder 331)
  - Bard College, B-0407, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 332)
  - Bard Graduate Center for Studies in the Decorative Arts, DF-0223, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 333)
  - Barnard College, B-0308, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 334)
  - Baruch College, B-0568, 2005-2007 (Box 30, Folder 335)
  - Baruch College, B-0568, Contested Spaces in Post-Soviet Art, Pictures by Robin Graubarb (Box 30, Folder 335)
  - Baryshnikov Dance Foundation, B-0348, 2003-2006 (Box 30, Folder 336)
  - Battery Dance Company, B-0203, 2000, 2002-2003, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 337)
  - Bennington College, DF-0303, 2002-2004, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 338)
  - Beringa South, DF-0650, 2006-2008 (Box 31, Folder 339)
  - Big Art Group, B-0448, 2004-2005, 2007, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 340)
  - Big Sky Conservation Institute, B-0432, 2004-2006 (Box 31, Folder 341)
  - Big Sky Conservation Institute, B-0432, GIS Seminar Photos, Gorno-Altaisk, Altai Republic (Box 31, Folder 341)
  - Big Sky Conservation Institute, B-0527, 2004-2006 (Box 31, Folder 342)
  - Big Sky Conservation Institute, B-0527, Big Sky Conservation Institute, TMU Photos, 2005-2006 (Box 31, Folder 342)
  - Bill Young & Dancers, B-0349, 1987, 1989-1991, 1993-1995, 1998, 2003-2008 (Box 31, Folder 343)
  - Blue Sky Gallery, DF-0336, 2003-2004 (Box 31, Folder 344)
  - Bond Street Theatre Coalition, B-0118, 2000-2002 (Box 31, Folder 345)
  - Bond Street Theatre Coalition, B-0236, 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 346)
  - Bond Street Theatre Coalition, EC-0417, 2004-2006 (Box 31, Folder 347)
  - Boston Cyberarts, Inc., DF-0503, 2003-2005, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 348)
  - Boston Cyberarts, Inc., DF-0503, Fico Balet, Ideas in Motion, Boston Cyberarts (Box 31, Folder 348)
  - Boston Cyberarts, Inc., DF-0503, Boston Cyberarts, Fico Balet, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 348)
  - Boston Cyberarts, Inc., Kinodance, B-0623, 2006-2008 (Box 31, Folder 349)
  - Boston Cyberarts, Inc., Kinodance, B-0623, Denizen (Sketch, Work-in-Progress), Alla Kovgan, NTSC (Box 31, Folder 349)
  - Boston Cyberarts, Inc., Kinodance, B-0623, Denizen, An Expanded Cinema Performance, NTSC, 2007 May (Box 31, Folder 349)
  - Boston Cyberarts, Inc., Kinodance, B-0623, Kinodance Co., Armenia, 2006 October (Box 31, Folder 349)
  - Boston Early Music Festival and Exhibition, B-0507, 2003-2006, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 350)
  - Boston Early Music Festival and Exhibition, Miscellaneous, B-0507, 2004-2005 (Box 32, Folder 351)
  - Boston Early Music Festival and Exhibition, EC-0505, 2003-2005, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 352)
  - Boston Symphony Orchestra, B-0141, 2001-2002 (Box 32, Folder 353)
  - Boston Symphony Orchestra, B-0237, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 354)
  - Boston University, Ballets Russes, B-0807, 2007-2008 (Box 32, Folder 355)
  - Boston University, Ballets Russes, Miscellaneous, B-0807, 2007, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 356)
  - Boston University, Educational Bridge Project, B-0101, 2000-2002 (Box 32, Folder 357)
  - Boston University, Educational Bridge Project, B-0142, 2001-2002 (Box 32, Folder 358)
  - Boston University, Educational Bridge Project, B-0186, 2001-2002 (Box 32, Folder 359)
  - Boston University, Educational Bridge Project. B-0238, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 360)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM), B-0187, 2001-2003, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 361)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM), B-0259, 2000-2004 (Box 32, Folder 362)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM), B-0310, 2002-2004, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 363)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM), Don Juan, B-0608, 2003, 2005-2007 (Box 33, Folder 364)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM), Don Juan, Miscellaneous, B-0608, 2006-2007 (Box 33, Folder 365)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM), B-0711, 2006-2008 (Box 33, Folder 366)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM), Miscellaneous, B-0711, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 367)
  - Brushy Fork Institute, B-0229, 2002-2005 (Box 33, Folder 368)
  - Brushy Fork Institute, B-0229, Pictures from Sustaining Indigenous Russian Communities (SIRC), 2003 (Box 33, Folder 368)
  - Byrd Hoffman Watermill Foundation, Russian Madness, B-0143, 2001, 2006-2007 (Box 33, Folder 369)
  - Byrd Hoffman Watermill Foundation, B-0409, 2003-2005 (Box 33, Folder 370)
  - California Cultures in Comparative Perspective, B-0528, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 371)
  - California Institute of the Arts, DF-0618, 2005-2008 (Box 33, Folder 372)
  - California Institute of the Arts, DF-0618, Cal Arts, Roman Stolyar, Photos by Scott Groller, 2007 April (Box 33, Folder 372)
  - California Institute of the Arts, Miscellaneous, DF-0618, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 373)
  - California Institute of the Arts, DF-0736, 2007-2008 (Box 33, Folder 374)
  - Carnegie Museum of Art, DF-0407, 2004-2005 (Box 34, Folder 375)
  - Carnegie Museum of Art, DF-0741, 2007-2009 (Box 34, Folder 376)
  - Catholic University of America, B-0119, 2000-2001, 2003, 2006-2007 (Box 34, Folder 377)
  - Catholic University of America, B-0544, 2002-2003, 2005-2008 (Box 34, Folder 378)
  - Catholic University of America, B-0544, Defiant Requiem at Terezin, Photos, 2006 May 21 (Box 34, Folder 378)
  - Catholic University of America, B-0544, Defiant Requiem, Prague, CUA Trip, 2006 May (Box 34, Folder 378)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Alfredo Jaar & Yulia Tikhonova, DF-0734, 2007-2008 (Box 34, Folder 379)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Alfredo Jaar & Yulia Tikhonova, DF-0734, Report Trust for Mutual Understanding A. Jaar Lecture/Master Class, Moscow, 2008 April (Box 34, Folder 379)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Alfredo Jaar & Yulia Tikhonova, Miscellaneous, DF-0734, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 380)
  - CEC ArtsLink, American Season, B-0754, 2006-2008 (Box 34, Folder 381)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Arts Leadership Fellowship, B-0714, 2006-2008 (Box 34, Folder 382)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Arts Leadership Fellows, B-0858, 2006-2008 (Box 34, Folder 383)
  - CEC Artslink, ArtsLink 2004, B-0405, 2003-2005 (Box 34, Folder 384)
  - CEC Artslink, ArtsLink 2004, B-0405, CEC ArtsLink, Center for Puppetry Arts, in E/CE (Box 34, Folder 384)
  - CEC ArtsLink, ArtsLink 2004, B-0405, CEC ArtsLink Images (Box 34, Folder 384)
  - CEC ArtsLink, ArtsLink 2004, Miscellaneous, B-0405 (Box 34, Folder 385)
  - CEC ArtsLink, ArtsLink 2005, B-0502, 2004-2006 (Box 35, Folder 386)
  - CEC ArtsLink, ArtsLink, Miscellaneous, B-0502, 2004-2005 (Box 35, Folder 387)
  - CEC ArtsLink, ArtsLink 2006, B-0603, 2005-2007 (Box 35, Folder 388)
  - CEC ArtsLink, CEC ArtsLink 2006 "ArtsLink", B-0603, Images (Box 35, Folder 388)
  - CEC ArtsLink, ArtsLink Awards, B-0706, 2006-2008 (Box 35, Folder 389)
  - CEC ArtsLink, ArtsLink Award, B-0802, ArtsLink VisArt (Box 35, Folder 389)
  - CEC ArtsLink, ArtsLink Awards, B-0802, 2007-2009 (Box 35, Folder 390)
  - CEC ArtsLink, ArtsLink Exhibition, EC-0318, 2003-2006 (Box 35, Folder 391)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Artspace, B-0655, 2006-2008 (Box 35, Folder 392)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Beth Custer Ensemble, B-0656, 2000-2001, 2005-2008 (Box 35, Folder 393)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Black Alphabet, B-0610, 2006-2007 (Box 35, Folder 394)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Black Alphabet, B-0610, Black Alphabet Documentation (Box 35, Folder 394)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Black Alphabet, B-0610, Black Alphabet Documentation, I Copy (Box 35, Folder 394)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Chris Reitz, DF-0620, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 395)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Chris Reitz, DF-0620, Sokol Beqiri Video (Box 36, Folder 395)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Chris Reitz, DF-0620, Erfort Kuke, Countdown Party (Box 36, Folder 395)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Chris Reitz, DF-0620, Alban Hajdinaj, Eye to Eye (Box 36, Folder 395)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Chris Reitz, DF-0620, Jakup Ferri, Video Works (Box 36, Folder 395)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Chris Reitz, DF-0620, Alban Hajdinaj, No Surprises, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 395)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Christian Nguyen, DF-0637, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 396)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Contemporary American Music, B-0810, 2008-2009 (Box 36, Folder 397)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Don Juan in Prague, EC-0518, 2005-2007 (Box 36, Folder 398)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Don Juan in Prague, Miscellaneous, EC-0518, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 399)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Don Juan in Prague, B-0613, EC-0616, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 400)
  - CEC ArtsLink, David Eden and Nigel Redden, DF-0709, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 401)
  - CEC ArtsLink, FlipFest, B-0808, 2007-2009 (Box 36, Folder 402)
  - CEC ArtsLink, FlipFest, B-0808, FlipFest! Photos (Box 36, Folder 402)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Flipside, B-0410, 2003-2006 (Box 36, Folder 403)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Fritzie Brown & Tamalyn Miller, Eastern & Central Europe, DF-0805, 2007-2008 (Box 36, Folder 404)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Gdansk Shipyard Health and Safety Exhibition, B-0446, 2003-2004, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 405)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Gdansk Shipyard Health and Safety Exhibition, B-0446, Health and Safety Images (Box 36, Folder 405)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Georgian Quintet Urmuli, B-0755, 2007-2008 (Box 36, Folder 406)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Hajnalka Somogyi, DF-0817, 2007-2008 (Box 36, Folder 407)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Jubilee Fellowships, B-0450, 2004-2007 (Box 36, Folder 408)
  - CDC ArtsLink, Jubilee Fellowships, B-0450, Jubilee Fellowships 2004 Photos (Box 36, Folder 408)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Long Arms Festival, B-0609, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 409)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Long Arms Festival, Nick Dmitriev, EC-0414, 2003-2006 (Box 37, Folder 410)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Luchezar Boyajiev, DF-0502, 2005, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 411)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Maka Dvalishvilli, DF-0401, 2003-2004, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 412)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Maria Brewinska, DF-0532, 2005-2006, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 413)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Maria Brewinska, Miscellaneous, DF-0532, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 414)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Maria Brewinska, Miscellaneous, DF-0532, Zacheta Narodowa Galeria Sztuki, Raport Roczny, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 414)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Maria Brewinska, Miscellaneous, DF-0532, Zacheta Narodowa Galeria Sztuki, Program I Oferta Sponsoringowa, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 414)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Mary Kelly, On Fidelity, DF-0811, 2008-2009 (Box 37, Folder 415)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Mary Kelly, DF-0811, Mary Kelly, Words Are Things, 2008 March 28-June 8 (Box 37, Folder 415)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Mary Kelly, DF-0811, Mary Kelly, Words Are Things, Mary Kelly Exhibit, Symposium in Poland, 2008 March 28-June 8 (Box 37, Folder 415)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Miscellaneous, 1999-2001, 2003, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 416)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Moscow Biennial, EC-0415, 2003-2005, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 417)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Museum Licensing and Merchandising, B-0352, 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 418)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Museum Partnerships, B-0351, 2003-2007 (Box 37, Folder 419)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Novosibirsk Biennale, B-0712, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 420)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Olga Kopenkina, "Post Diasporas", DF-0424, 2004-2005 (Box 37, Folder 421)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Olga Kopenkina, "Post Diasporas", Miscellaneous, DF-0424, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 422)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Olga Kopenkina, "Significant Others", DF-0540, 2005-2007 (Box 37, Folder 423)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Olga Kopenkina, "Significant Others", Miscellaneous, DF-0540, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 424)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Olga Kopenkina, "Significant Others", Miscellaneous, DF-0540, Russia, Significant Others, O. Kopenkina (Box 37, Folder 424)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Olga Manulkina, DF-0506, 2004-2005 (Box 38, Folder 425)
  - CEC ArtsLink, OpenLook, DF-0619, 2003, 2006-2007 (Box 38, Folder 426)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Patriarchate Choir, B-0654, 2005-2007 (Box 38, Folder 427)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Patriarchate Choir, Miscellaneous, B-0654, 2007-2008 (Box 38, Folder 428)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Prague Quadrennial, B-0612, 2006-2008 (Box 38, Folder 429)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Prague Quadrennial, B-0612, PQ, Foto I, 2007 June 14-24 (Box 38, Folder 429)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Prague Quadrennial, B-0612, PQ, Foto II, 2007 June 14-24 (Box 38, Folder 429)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Prague Quadrennial, B-0612, PQ, Foto III, 2007 June 14-24 (Box 38, Folder 429)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Prague Quadrennial, Miscellaneous, B-0612, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 430)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Russian Contemporary Art Journalists, B-0611, 2006-2008 (Box 38, Folder 431)
  - CEC ArtsLink, School for Missing Studies, B-0311, B-0402, 2002-2006 (Box 38, Folder 432)
  - CEC ArtsLink, School for Missing Studies B-0311, B-0402, Interactive Normalization Project's Website (Box 38, Folder 432)
  - CEC ArtsLink, School for Missing Studies B-0311, B-0402, Interactive Normalization (Disk 2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 429)
  - CEC ArtsLink, School for Missing Studies B-0311, B-0402, Project Go_Home, Website (Box 38, Folder 429)
  - CEC ArtsLink, School for Missing Studies B-0311, B-0402, Interactive Normalization (Disk 1 of 2), 2002 November 21 (Box 38, Folder 429)
  - CEC ArtsLink, School of Missing Studies, EC-0603, 2006-2008 (Box 38, Folder 433)
  - CEC ArtsLink, School of Missing Studies, Miscellaneous, EC-0603, 2004-2005 (Box 38, Folder 434)
  - CEC ArtsLink, School of Missing Studies, Miscellaneous, EC-0603, Looking For October, Film (Box 38, Folder 434)
  - CEC ArtsLink, School of Missing Studies, B-0809, 2007-2008 (Box 38, Folder 435)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Twelfth Night, US Tour 2006, B-0580, 2004-2006, 2008-2009 (Box 38, Folder 436)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Uncle Vanya, B-0856, DF-0910, 2005, 2008-2009 (Box 38, Folder 437)
  - CEC ArtsLink, US Presenters to Georgia,EC-0507, 2005-2008 (Box 38, Folder 438)
  - CEC ArtsLink, USA Moscow, Moscow Biennial, EC-0647, 2006-2008 (Box 38, Folder 439)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Vadim Kasparov, DF-0607, 2005-2006 (Box 39, Folder 440)
  - CEC ArtsLink, VisArt 2005, B-0451, 2004-2006 (Box 39, Folder 441)
  - CEC ArtsLink, VisArt 2005, B-0451, Public Art, VisArt, Photos (Box 39, Folder 441)
  - CEC ArtsLink, VisArt 2005, B-0451, VisArt, Photos (Box 39, Folder 441)
  - CEC ArtsLink, VisArt 2006, B-0604, 2005-2008 (Box 39, Folder 442)
  - CEC ArtsLink, VisArt, DF-0811, 2007-2009 (Box 39, Folder 443)
  - CEC ArtsLink, VisArt, CEC ArtsLink, VisArt & Art Leaders Fellows (ALF), 2008 (Box 39, Folder 443)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Vis-Art Special Projects, B-0713, 2006-2009 (Box 39, Folder 444)
  - CEC ArtsLink, Visual Arts Exchange, Serbia & Croatia, DF-0432, 2004-2005 (Box 39, Folder 445)
  - CEC International Partners, Artslink 2002, B-0200, 2001-2003 (Box 39, Folder 446)
  - CEC International Partners, ArtsLink, B-0303, 2001-2004 (Box 39, Folder 447)
  - CEC International Partners, ArtsLink, Go-Home, B-0103, 1999-2004 (Box 40, Folder 448)
  - CEC International Partners, Balanchine in Perm, B-0102, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 449)
  - CEC International Partners, Boris Godunov, B-0313, 2001-2003, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 450)
  - CEC International Partners, Charlotte Cohen, DF-0133, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 451)
  - CEC International Partners, Charlotte Cohen, DF-0333, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 452)
  - CEC International Partners, Charlotte Cohen Belgrade Public Art, EC-0210, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 453)
  - CEC International Partners, Civil Society Development Foundation, DF-0118, 2000-2001, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 454)
  - CEC International Partners, Contemporary Music Program, B-0240, 2001+-2005 (Box 40, Folder 455)
  - CEC International Partners, EVO 1, B-0144, 2000-2002 (Box 40, Folder 456)
  - CEC International Partners, Heart of the Prague Quadrennial, EC-0304, 2002-2004 (Box 40, Folder 457)
  - CEC International Partners, Interactive Normalization Project, DF-0224, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 458)
  - CEC International Partners, Interactive Normalization, Miscellaneous, DF-0224, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 459)
  - CEC International Partners, Jubilee Fellows, EC-0302, 2002-2005 (Box 41, Folder 460)
  - CEC International Partners, Museum Licensing and Merchandising, B-0241, 2001-2005 (Box 41, Folder 461)
  - CEC International Partners, New Deal Cinema, B-0302, 2002-2004 (Box 41, Folder 462)
  - CEC International Partners, Philip Glass, B-0208, 2001-2004 (Box 41, Folder 463)
  - CEC International Partners, Polish-American Curators Exchange, EC-0303, 2003-2004 (Box 41, Folder 464)
  - CEC International Partners, Programs Evaluation, B-0312, 2002-2006 (Box 41, Folder 465)
  - CEC International Partners, St. Petersburg Capella, B-0279, 2001-2003, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 466)
  - CEC International Partners, St. Petersburg 2003, Parallel Fund, B-9864, B-9966, B-0076, B-0179, B-0243, 1998-2004 (Box 42, Folder 467-468)
  - CEC International Partners, St. Petersburg 2003, Parallel Fund, Year 3, B-0076, 2000-2001 (Box 42, Folder 469-470)
  - CEC International Partners, St. Petersburg 2003, Parallel Fund, Year 4, B-0179, 2001-2002 (Box 42, Folder 471)
  - CEC International Partners, St. Petersburg 2003, Parallel Fund, Year 5, B-0243, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 472)
  - CEC International Partners, St. Petersburg 2003, Parallel Fund, Miscellaneous, B-9864, B-9966, B-0076, B-0179, B-0243, 1992-1994, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 473)
  - CEC International Partners, St. Petersburg 2003, Parallel Fund, American Committee for St. Petersburg 2003, 1999-2000, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 474)
  - CEC International Partners, St. Petersburg 2003, Parallel Fund, St. Petersburg Cultural Fund, 1998-1999 (Box 43, Folder 475)
  - CEC International Partners, St. Petersburg 2003, Parallel Fund, St. Petersburg: A Cultural Celebration, Final Report, 1997 January 14-March 9 (Box 43, Folder 476)
  - CEC International Partners, Theater Management Project, Russia, B-0188, 2000-2004 (Box 43, Folder 477)
  - CEC International Partners, Travel Grant for Rob Storr, DF-0309, 2002-2003, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 478)
  - CEC International Partners, VisArt, B-0120, 2001-2004 (Box 43, Folder 479)
  - CEC International Partners, VisArt, Miscellaneous, B-0120, 2001-2002 (Box 43, Folder 480)
  - CEC International Partners, VisArt, B-0280, 2002-2005 (Box 43, Folder 481-482)
  - CEC International Partners, VisArt, Miscellaneous, B-0280, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 483)
  - Center for Clean Air Policy, EC-0314, 2003-2004 (Box 44, Folder 484)
  - Center for Creative Resources, DF-0612, 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 485)
  - Center for Creative Resources, DF-0735, 2007-2008 (Box 44, Folder 486)
  - Center for Creative Resources, DF-0735, Janis Brenner and Dancers, Promo DVD, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 486)
  - Center for Democracy, EC-0107, 1995, 1998, 2000-2002, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 487)
  - Center for Democracy, EC-0215, 1995, 1998, 2000, 2002-2003, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 488)
  - Center for Government and Public Policy Analysis, DF-0318, 2003-2004 (Box 44, Folder 489)
  - Center for Government and Public Policy Analysis, Miscellaneous, DF-0318, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 490)
  - Center for International Theatre Development, B-0121, B-0202, 2000-2002, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 491-492)
  - Center for International Theatre Development, DF-0107, 2001, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 493)
  - Center for International Theatre Development, B-0281, B-0304, 2002-2004, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 494)
  - Center for International Theatre Development, B-0503, B-0600, 2004-2006, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 495)
  - Center for International Theatre Development, Miscellaneous, B-0503, B-0600, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 496)
  - Center for International Theatre Development Miscellaneous, B-0503, B-0600, Apart Theatre Group, Doors, Moscow Tallinn, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 496)
  - Center for International Theatre Development, DF-0528, 2004-2006, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 497)